slungo.com 2014-11-20

# Privacy Policy - Slungo

**W** e respect the privacy of of all internet users. 

**Information collected**   
When you visit our website we collect some information from you. We collect no personally identifiable information such as your name, address, phone number, or e-mail address unless you willingly submit it to us via registration or contact. Some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider you use to connect to the internet, your browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use is collected upon your visit to our site in order to provide our advertisers with targeting information. 

**I** f you were sent to our site from one of our partner sites and if you get sent to one of our partners from this site a non harmful cookie is added to your internet browser. These non-malicious cookies are set to delete themselves 1-24 hours after they have been created. 

**W** e allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org. 

**W** e might use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our websites. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, 

[click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

**A Special Note About Children**   
Children are not eligible to use our services unsupervised and we ask that children (under the age of 14) do not submit any personal information to us. If you are a minor, you can use this service only in conjunction with permission and guidance from your parents or guardians. 

**Acquisition or Changes in Ownership**   
In the event that the web site (or a substantial portion of its assets) is acquired, your information would be considered part of those assets, and may be part of those assets that are transferred. 

**Policy Modifications**   
We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If/when changes are made to this privacy policy, we will email users who have given us permission to do so. We will post any changes here, so be sure to check back periodically. However, please be assured that if the Privacy Policy changes in the future, we will not use the personal information you have submitted to us under this Privacy Policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this Privacy Policy, without your prior consent.
